[sinister music playing]
[thunder roaring]
[fire crackling]
[distinct screams]
Help!
No! Please, no!
Please, no!
[Sarah screams]
[soft music playing]
♪ It will joy
and comfort give you ♪
♪ Take it then
wherever you go ♪
-♪ Precious name ♪
-♪ Oh, how sweet ♪
♪ Hope of Earth
and joy of Heav'n ♪
-♪ Precious name ♪
-♪ Oh, how sweet ♪
[coughs]
♪ Hope of Earth
and joy of Heav'n... ♪
That's beautiful. What is it?
Sarah's favorite.
She'd climb up
on the dining room table
and sing that hymn
every time we had guests.
Oh.
[coughs]
Here you are.
Oh, thank you.
Julia.
Right.
Um, are those my keys?
No.
Evelyn.
I keep mace on there.
They're mine.
No.
I wouldn't want you
hurting yourself.
What?
Evelyn, please.
[keys jingle]
Thank you.
Why do you carry mace?
Um, I live alone, so.
But you live with me now.
[thunder roars]
It's getting late.
We should get you to bed soon.
I'll just check your
blood pressure first, okay?
Okay.
[thunder roaring]
I want you
to put your hand right here.
Hm.
Is that comfortable?
So, is Sarah your daughter?
You know, we never locked
our doors when we were young.
[chuckles]
We had no need to.
That must've been nice.
It was nice.
We'd be out all day,
wandering.
Come home in the evening
and our parents never worried.
Maybe they did.
Maybe you just didn't notice.
Maybe.
[apparatus inflates]
[apparatus deflates]
[thunder roaring]
Okay.
Am I okay?
Yeah. 116 over 75.
You're good.
Hmm.
Just hold on.
Okay.
[beep]
[thunder booming]
[beeps]
Good.
[thunder roaring]
There's a storm coming.
Yeah.
I was supposed
to fix your room.
Oh, it's fine.
My room was made up.
Thank you.
Are you done?
Yes.
Okay. That smells nice.
Mm-hmm.
Did we uh,
did I show you around?
I have everything I need.
Thank you.
All right. Hmm.
I forget sometimes.
How are you feeling?
Like hell.
Well, I'll be right
in the next room
if you need anything.
Thank you. Uh...
Julia.
Yes, Julia,
and I'm so sorry.
No. No apologies.
It's fine.
Goodnight.
Goodnight, Sarah.
[floor creaks]
[switch clicks]
[keys jingle]
[Evelyn]
Now I lay me down to sleep.
I pray for all
the souls I keep.
[thunder booms]
-[loud thud]
-Shit!
[clicks]
[thunder booms]
[phone rings]
[sighs]
[clicks switch]
[door closes]
[phone rings]
Uh, shit.
[dialing tone]
[clears throat]
Hi, Dad.
[indistinct speech on phone]
No, I'm not ignoring you.
I'm working.
No, Dad,
I told you I probably--
I'm not gonna make it.
[indistinct speech on phone]
I'm not avoiding it.
[scoffs]
It's just,
I-- I just got this job.
I can't leave a few days in.
[indistinct speech on phone]
I don't know.
I can't believe
you're asking this.
[indistinct speech on phone]
Dad, I don't know.
[scoffs]
Ew.
No, never mind.
I said I don't know,
because it's not
that kind of job.
It could be a few days,
a few weeks.
[dishes clatter]
Of course, I miss her.
What kind of question is that?
Yeah, I get it, but...
[water runs]
Well, what does it matter?
No one's seen me there
in years.
[thunder roars]
Uh, Dad, come on.
I don't go anymore.
You know that.
[indistinct speech on phone]
[door shuts and locks]
Well, what difference
does it make?
It doesn't change anything.
Mom knew I loved her!
[indistinct speech on phone]
Dad? Dad?
Listen, I need to go,
so I'll call you again tomorrow
and we can talk
about this then, okay?
-[thunder booms]
-[indistinct speech on phone]
Yes, I promise.
[indistinct speech on phone]
Okay.
I love you, too.
Okay, bye.
[clicks]
[can pops open]
[slurps]
[phone rings]
Jesus.
Like, what is not clear about,
I'll call you to--
[Evelyn]
What are you doing
in my house?
Evelyn?
How do you know my name?
I'm your nurse.
I just helped you to bed.
We spoke about Sarah,
your daughter.
How about you
give me that, yeah?
Let's put it back
by the fireplace.
What do you think?
Yeah? Please.
Did you paint that?
Yes.
Very talented.
I'm quite terrible.
You're an artist?
Nothing serious.
Are those yours, too?
Mm-hmm.
I'd love to see
your other paintings.
-You can hold onto that
if it makes you feel better.
-Mm-hmm.
Is that okay?
Okay.
Go first.
Right. Yeah, sure.
Okay.
Wow.
I love the-- the detail
on this one.
Mm.
You have a real eye for color.
The way they
contrast each other.
I would've never guessed
these go together, but they do.
My mom taught me everything.
She had an eye like you do.
Is this you?
Long time ago.
And that's your family?
Yeah.
Hmm.
Anthropology.
That's the study
of culture, right?
Art and rituals,
and things like that?
Oh, Randall gave me that
for our first anniversary.
He got it at a, uh,
an art supply store
and then he buried it
at our picnic spot.
Is Randall the guy in the photo?
Yeah. He-- he painted, too,
but he took this photograph
of me just before our wedding.
That's the biggest smile
I've ever seen.
Yeah.
He must've been very special.
We were happy.
Hey, it's getting late.
How about we get back,
we get you back to bed?
I'll put this back.
[thunder booming]
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
Julia?
Yeah.
[ominous music playing]
You okay?
Watch your step.
Here we are.
There you go.
Oh.
[giggles]
Thank you, Julia.
What happened to your hands?
Oh.
Oh, nothing.
Just old scars.
Hmm.
[exhales]
That is one gorgeous necklace.
Oh, why thank you.
It was my mother's.
Is that gold?
Um, I think so, yeah.
What a lovely piece.
Oh, my.
Do you think
you could help me down?
Of course.
[clears throat]
That's it. There we go.
Oh, my.
Ooh, you know,
all my bones creak.
[chuckles]
Okay.
Ooh.
Hmm, pray with me.
[Julia]
Pardon?
[taps]
Pray with me.
I used to think that
prayer was ridiculous, too,
before Sarah,
but somehow asking
an all-powerful being
for something seems arrogant.
Hmm.
But there is grace
in supplication.
Hmm?
I don't really pray
to God anymore.
Who said anything about God?
[thunder roars]
Thank you, dear.
Now clasp your hands.
Now I lay me down to sleep.
Go on.
[clears throat]
I pray for all the souls I keep.
If I should die
before I wake,
I pray the souls
another body will take.
If I should live
for a few more days,
I pray my keeper
to guide my ways.
In my name,
I pray,
I pray.
Now I lay me down to sleep.
I pray for all
of the souls I keep.
If I should die
before I wake,
I pray the souls
another body will take.
If I should live
for a few more days,
I pray my keeper
to guide my way.
Okay.
[thunder booms]
Yeah.
Uh, yeah, I'll just...
Later.
[water runs]
[thunder booms]
[sniffs]
Not bad.
That's cute.
[sniffs]
That's gross.
[thunder booms]
Color contrast, my ass.
You're one dark lady.
[Evelyn coughs]
Yeah, you're okay.
[floor creaks]
[sinister music playing]
Weird.
[thunder booms]
[thud upstairs]
[winds howling]
[sinister music playing]
[gulps]
[slurps]
[music continues to play]
[house creaking]
[clock ticking]
[Julia clears throat]
[thunder roaring]
[sighs]
[clock ticking]
[creaking sounds]
-[loud thunder]
-[thudding sounds]
[creaking continues]
[thudding]
[loud thunder]
[floor creaks above]
[sinister music playing]
Evelyn? Are you up again?
[knocking sound]
[knocking continues]
[sinister music playing]
Can I help you?
Is Evelyn home?
Sorry, who are you?
Randall.
You're Julia, right?
Your agency put us in touch.
Yeah, yeah.
Of course, hi.
Come in.
[door shuts]
You're Evelyn's husband.
Well, not for a long time now.
Oh.
Is she up?
I just put her to bed.
I hope she's awake.
I drove a long way out.
She should be.
She was just praying, so...
Evie, praying?
Yeah.
[Julia clears throat]
Did you-- did you hit the storm
on the way here?
No, I came
from the other direction.
I hope it doesn't get too bad.
How is she doing?
Uh, it's been
a pretty rough night.
She's been kind of in and out.
She spoke about you, though.
Is something wrong?
No.
Uh, no. It's just,
I haven't seen this one
in a long time.
[footsteps]
[sinister music playing]
[floor creaks]
[music continues to play]
There she is.
Randall?
Hey, Evie.
Huh.
You got old.
Yeah, they say that happens.
You're still as lovely as ever.
And you're still full of shit.
[chuckles]
I've missed you.
I know.
Is Earl here with you?
My brother died 12 years ago.
You went to the funeral.
I did?
It's okay.
None of us are
what we used to be, right?
And Marlene?
She left me.
That's been
a long time now, too.
I'm sorry.
[chuckles]
No, you're not.
No, I'm not.
[chuckles]
How long are you staying?
As long as I need to.
You have help now,
so you don't need to worry
about anything.
You have been thinking
about her.
Every day.
Me too.
So why are you here?
[paper shuffles]
Where did you find
this inscription?
Why didn't you wait
for me to get back?
We could've discussed it,
figured out something together.
Where is it, Evelyn?
I know you have it.
No.
Nobody else knows
where we buried it.
No. No.
-Why would you take it?
-No.
If it's for this,
you know what can happen.
-Where is it?
-[Julia] Hey.
Go away.
I'm trying to protect you!
-No.
-Hey! Don't touch her.
Leave me, leave me,
leave me alone.
[Evelyn crying]
[Evelyn]
Go away.
You need to leave.
Now.
[Evelyn sobs]
[Evelyn]
Make him go. Make him go.
Okay.
[Evelyn]
Make sure he leaves.
[Julia]
I promise.
[Evelyn]
I don't wanna see him.
If you don't get out
of this house in 30 seconds,
I'm calling the police.
I don't care who you are.
You have no idea
what's going on here.
[Evelyn groans]
[Julia]
Yeah.
It's gonna be okay, all right?
[Evelyn]
Please, please get rid of him.
I never wanna see him again.
[Julia]
All right, just--
just calm down.
I'll be right back.
Where are you hiding it?
[Julia]
Hey! Get out!
[sinister music playing]
Just leave!
Watch yourself.
[locking]
[sinister music playing]
[car starts]
[car drives away]
[thunder roars]
[wind whooshes]
Evelyn, what are you doing?
It's freezing.
[Evelyn] I wanna be out here
when I pass.
[Julia] Let's not talk about
that. You've still got time.
[Evelyn] Why would anyone
want a job like this?
Why would you want to
watch someone die?
[Julia] Because no one
should have to die alone.
[Evelyn] We all die alone.
[Julia] What was that all
about up there?
[Evelyn] Oh,
we don't agree on things.
We never did, really.
I tried to get him
to understand
but he-- he blames me.
[Julia] What happened to Sarah?
[Evelyn] Oh, Sarah.
I miss her so much.
Can't hide from our past.
Sometimes we have
to confront it and accept it.
[Julia] Is everything okay?
[Evelyn] I'm going to be sick.
[Julia] Come on,
let's go inside.
[Evelyn groans]
[throws up]
Oh, dear. Come here.
[groans]
Ugh, oh, I'm so sorry.
No, it's okay. It's fine.
Let's get you cleaned up, okay?
I'll find you a blanket.
[sinister music playing]
All right.
Evelyn?
[clattering noises in distance]
Oh, my... Evelyn?
[Evelyn snarls]
Evelyn, what are you doing?
[snarling]
Stop that, please.
[growls, snarls]
[pants]
Evelyn!
[footsteps thud away]
[Evelyn laughs]
[Julia]
Stop.
[loud thuds]
Eve--
[record playing in background]
Jesus Christ.
[Sarah on recorder]
It's not working.
[Evelyn on recorder]
The song will work.
It always works.
[Sarah on recorder]
Brush my hair.
What the fuck is this?
[Evelyn on recorder]
Sure, my love.
[Sarah on recorder]
It don't feel so good.
My tummy hurts.
[Evelyn on recorder]
Do you want me
to rub your tummy?
[Sarah on recorder]
Mom?
[Evelyn on recorder]
What is it?
[Sarah on recorder]
Why do you have that?
[Evelyn on recorder]
Oh, this?
[Sarah on recorder]
Are you taping me?
-[Evelyn on recorder] I...
-[Julia] Where the fuck am I?
[Evelyn on recorder]
I was-- I was worried about you
and wanted to record
any changes.
[Sarah on recorder]
Changes?
[Evelyn on recorder]
Sorry, I should've asked you.
I'll turn it off.
[Sarah on recorder]
Is it off?
[Evelyn on recorder]
Yes.
[Sarah on recorder]
Don't ever do that again!
-[tape clatters]
-shit.
[Evelyn on recorder]
Sarah?
[Sarah on recorder]
Get out!
[Evelyn on recorder]
I'm sorry.
[clicks recorder off]
[sinister music playing]
[Julia]
Okay.
[sinister music playing]
Oh, my God, Evelyn,
what did you do?
[ominous music playing]
What the hell?
[sinister music playing]
What is this?
[music continues to play]
[ominous music playing]
[Julia clears throat]
[footsteps shuffling]
[floor creaks]
Hello?
[door creaks]
What... What is...
[soft gasps]
What the fuck?
[sinister music playing]
[loud thud]
[Peter]
Is there a back door?
[Randall]
I think I can open it.
Pete!
Go check upstairs.
Sh-- shit.
Oh!
[footsteps approach]
[clicks switch]
[sinister music playing]
[Peter]
Office is clear.
[Randall]
Kitchen's clear.
Evelyn, where are you?
I just want to talk!
[sinister music playing]
[door creaks open]
Okay.
[thunder booms]
[floor creaking]
Hey.
[screams]
Oh, fuck! Oh!
[Edgar coughing]
[panting]
Calm down.
Where do I go?
Where the fuck do I go?
Shit!
Okay, okay.
Just find something.
There's gotta be something
in here.
Okay. Find scissors.
Okay.
Shit.
Fucking...
Fucking shit!
[Edgar]
She blinded me, man.
[Peter]
Yeah, well.
-[Edgar] I'm scared.
-[Randall] Quiet!
[Edgar]
It fucking burns!
[Randall] Hey, man up!
You grab him.
I can't look
for anyone right now.
Hey, shut up. All right?
Just be quiet.
We just want to talk.
We're running out of time.
Give me a minute.
Go downstairs.
I'm not gonna hurt anybody.
Can we talk?
I'd like to explain.
Stay away!
This is not how
I wanted this to go.
How did you
want this to go?
This is a misunderstanding.
Just leave us alone!
You can stay in there
if it makes you feel better.
It does.
Evelyn's in trouble.
Where is she?
I don't know!
And I wouldn't tell you
if I did.
Is she still in the house?
What the fuck did I just say?
Nothing I can tell you will
make you believe me.
Hell, I didn't believe it myself
and I lived through it.
Through what?
[sighs]
We had a child.
She died because
we couldn't protect her.
That's a lie.
We could've protected her,
but we got careless.
We thought we knew better
and it destroyed us.
Evelyn never forgave herself
and...
And what?
She was my first love,
you know?
[Peter]
Randall, we got her!
Just leave her alone!
I'm sorry.
This is for your own good.
[door locks shut]
Let me out!
[lock rattling]
[Edgar]
Randall, Peter, we got her.
Calm down.
[Evelyn]
Get out of my house!
[Randall]
Take a deep breath.
Calm down.
[Evelyn]
Don't touch me.
Everything is gonna be okay.
[Evelyn]
Of course, it's you.
Stay away.
Peter, give her some space.
Evelyn, put that down.
You shouldn't be touching that.
Please, hand it over, Evie.
Let me take it off your hands.
I just want to put it
someplace safe.
[Evelyn]
There is no place safe.
It was safe until you started
messing with it.
Why, Evie?
[Evelyn]
Because I miss her!
I'm sorry about
the way things turned out.
Yeah, you left me
right after she died
when I needed you the most.
[sobs]
What do you want me to say?
That I couldn't face you after?
That the-- the guilt
ate me up inside?
I got it wrong and I've had
to live with that.
But I can do it right this time.
I know how. Trust me.
Trust you?
That's what got her killed.
I translated one of the words
that you sent me.
[paper shuffles]
It's an incantation, isn't it?
Tell me!
We can still do the right thing.
That's your weakness, always
wanting to do the right thing,
huh, when there's only pain
and loss and suffering.
This is not going
to bring Sarah back!
Give it to me!
Why? [voice deepening]
So you can bury me again?
[Randall]
Who-- who am I talking
to right now?
What have you done with Evelyn?
I wear her like a coat.
[growls]
[coughs]
[body thuds]
[yells, groans]
Oh, my God.
[Edgar]
Let's get outta here.
Oh, let's call the others.
Get out, quick, quick.
[fire crackling]
[Evelyn low giggling]
[dragging sounds]
[sinister music playing]
[groans]
[music continues to play]
[wind whooshes]
[clock ticking]
[exhales]
[ringing sound]
[sinister music playing]
[takes deep breath]
[clattering sounds]
[Julia]
Evelyn? Evelyn?
[footsteps]
Oh, my God,
what did they do to you?
They're gone now.
Let's get you changed.
Oh, my goodness.
Here we go.
Where are you hurt?
Oh, look at your hand.
What did they do to you?
Okay, let's-- let's sit here.
Yeah, there you go.
-Want to give me that?
-No.
Wash your hands, okay?
Okay. Okay. Here we go.
[water running]
All right. There you go.
Got this one.
That's great.
Where's your phone?
-In the office.
-Okay.
We'll find it, yeah?
You'll be okay.
Yeah.
Here we are. All right.
Okay, you good?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
-All right. Here we are.
All right.
Let's sit right here.
Where is it?
Okay, great.
For fuck's sake!
[slams phone]
What do they want?
What-- this?
What-- what is it?
Is it worth a lot of money?
[groans loudly]
[thunder rumbling]
This is not--
You should be surrounded
by loved ones,
not by someone like me.
[Evelyn on recorder]
Sarah, if you ever get
to hear this,
your suffering is
because of us.
Too many risks.
Too much contact
with the other side.
[Randall on recorder]
We have to bury her.
[Evelyn on recorder]
I'm sorry we put
all this ahead of you.
I'll never expose you
to this again.
What's wrong with us?
[Randall on recorder]
Okay. Father, start the prayer.
[father on recorder
speaking Latin]
[Evelyn on recorder]
I'm sorry.
It was meant for--
[Sarah on recorder]
Stop, stop.
Please don't do this.
[Evelyn on recorder]
I'm sorry.
Is that...
[Sarah on recorder]
Help me. Mommy!
-...your baby?
-No, mommy, please.
[Evelyn on recorder]
She's not okay.
[Randall on recorder]
She will be fine.
[Sarah on recorder]
Stop! Stop!
[Father on recorder]
She'll look in the box.
[Evelyn on recorder]
What-- what is this?
[indiscernible speech]
[Evelyn on recorder]
Look at her!
[Sarah on recorder]
Help!
[father on recorder
speaking Latin]
[Sarah on recorder]
Stop! Stop! Stop!
[Randall on recorder]
There he is.
[Sarah on recorder]
Get off!
[Randall on recorder]
We've got to bury the de--
Let's get you warmed up.
[humming]
I brought her to evil.
It's my fault.
-It's all my fault.
-Don't say that.
It's true.
All right. You're okay.
Okay.
No, no. I don't want it.
[pants]
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
You feeling better?
This one's nice.
[thunder rumbles]
Things happen, Evelyn.
I'm sure you and Randall
were great parents.
You don't know that.
I know I blamed myself
for my mom's death.
I mean, I know,
I didn't make her sick,
but I-- I should've been there
for her, and I-- I just-- I--
I couldn't do it.
It's easier to take care
of strangers.
Hmm.
[knocking on door]
Fuck's sake.
Just stay here.
[Randall]
I just want to talk!
Please just don't move!
[knocking on door]
I called the cops!
You need to get
the fuck outta here now!
Listen to me.
I know it's confusing, but--
but that's not Evelyn in there.
It's something dangerous.
The only dangerous thing here
is you and your psycho friends!
She killed Peter!
He's dead because of her!
She didn't kill anybody!
She's fucking old!
Stay the fuck back!
[slams, locks]
That little ivory statue
that she has,
you're not safe as long
as that thing is in the house.
The statue is the problem?
It's an anchor, a vessel
for something dark.
It's attached itself to her.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
It'll kill you both!
We can't leave here without--
Okay, fine!
If I get it for you,
will you leave?
Yes.
That's all we want!
Just stay outside.
I'll go get it!
You're doing the right thing.
[thunder rumbling]
[Evelyn] You think you can
take this from me?
Huh?
[Julia]
For fuck's sake, Evelyn,
I told you to stay over there!
Put the knife down!
No!
[Julia]
Please, let's talk.
Maybe we can work
something out with them.
Evelyn, everything's
gonna be okay.
You're safe.
Why don't you just give me--
No! No!
Evelyn, stop!
[Evelyn]
You, stop!
Evelyn, stop.
Where are you?
-Fuck.
-[Evelyn laughs]
[door creaks]
Evelyn?
[sinister music playing]
Hello?
[door creaks]
[music continues to play]
-[gasps]
-[Evelyn laughs]
[footsteps thud above]
[sinister music playing]
[loud thuds]
[thunder rumbles]
[Randall]
Hurry up!
Come on.
You're here.
We can still salvage this.
Trust me.
Like Peter did?
What is this?
What are we dealing
with, Randall?
Nothing I can't handle.
What happened?
We were too late.
It's already in her.
We lost Peter,
there was nothing we could do.
We need to get it
into the statue
and back in here.
Randall, this is very dangerous.
It's not because
I'm no longer authorized.
It's--
You remember what happened
last time we tried this?
You're all I've got.
I'm not gonna lose
both of them.
I understand.
Randall, this one,
this one is strong.
Stronger than anything
we ever faced before
and you know it.
-This time is different.
-What's this?
We can destroy it.
We only need one word.
This is an incantation
of the blood of Christ.
Blood of Christ.
Evelyn figured it out.
No more hiding it away.
I can finally make it pay
for everything that it's done.
Send it back to hell
where it belongs.
Hey, if this time
it doesn't work?
We're going through the front.
Stick together, near the back.
Holler if you see her.
Don't do anything
until I'm there.
Go on.
I'm going to fix this.
[sinister music playing]
She's stronger than she looks.
If it goes south,
just run out.
[rattling]
Evelyn, is that you?
[radio static]
[Randall on recording]
Honey, do you know
why you're here?
-[Sarah on recording]
Why-- why are my hands tied?
-What the hell?
[Evelyn on recording]
So you don't
hurt yourself again.
Remember last night?
[Sarah on recording]
No.
[Randall on recording]
You scratched
until your face bled.
[Sarah on recording]
Stop it.
[Sarah groans]
[Randall on recording]
How do you feel?
[Sarah on recording]
My tummy really hurts.
[loud growls]
[Sarah on recording]
I don't feel good.
[Evelyn on recording]
Do you remember
when we went on the dig?
what school you go to?
[Sarah on recording]
No! No!
[Evelyn on recording]
What do you remember?
[Sarah on recording]
No. Mommy!
[Evelyn on recording]
Sarah?
[Sarah on recording]
I pray the soul
is another body to take.
I only remember
that you're a shit mother!
- [Randall on recording]
Sarah!
- [slapping sound]
[Evelyn on recording]
Randall!
[evil laugh]
[Evelyn on recording]
Oh, my God.
[Sarah on recording]
Is that all you've got,
old man?
-Hmm?
-[Sarah laughs]
[Evelyn on recording]
Stop it!
[Sarah on recording]
No!
[Evelyn on recording]
Look at her!
[Sarah on recording]
No!
[Evelyn on recording]
What have we done?
[loud scream]
Shit.
[glass shatters in distance]
[knife clangs]
[sinister music playing]
Evelyn, where have you been?
[Evelyn] Why do you have that?
You're scaring me.
Please don't hurt me.
[voice deepening]
Why are you following me?
[Julia]
I was looking for you.
Where were you?
Do you remember anything?
I remember some things.
I had a dream about my mother,
not long after she passed.
We were making dinner together,
like every other night.
And right in the middle,
she stopped
and said she had to go.
So I ran after her
to say goodbye,
but she kept walking
like she didn't hear me.
So I followed her,
but she was lost,
disappeared into the fog.
[echoing]
[sniffling]
How do you know that?
I never told you that.
[Evelyn laughs]
[thunder booming]
[sinister music playing]
[Evelyn laughs]
[Evelyn]
I never told you that.
Evelyn?
Stop, you're freaking me out.
[Julia's Mom]
Jules? Jules.
Mom?
[Julia's Mom]
Can you come here, please?
I missed you, mija.
This can't...
[Julia's Mom]
The last time I saw you
was at the airport.
We were saying goodbye
and the sunlight
was shining behind you.
-And it was so beautiful.
-[Julia] You're not my mom.
[Julia's Mom] Oh, Jules,
remember when you were five
and broke your arm?
-Who fed you every meal?
-No. Stop it. Stop it.
Please, stop.
[Julia's Mom]
When you were 12 and missed
a month of school
with pneumonia,
who nursed you back to health?
Who cried with you
when your prom date
didn't show up?
-I held you. I comforted you.
-Stop.
-[Julia's Mom]
I was there for you.
-No puedo...
-[Julia's Mom]
It's so cold here.
-Stop it.
[Julia's Mom] Please.
Let me see you again.
I said stop it!
Te quiero, mija.
-[screams]
-[Evelyn laughs]
[body thuds]
[Julia groans]
[sinister music playing]
[screams]
Okay.
[crying]
Oh, okay.
[groans]
[lock rattling]
Okay.
[panting]
Oh, what is this?
[sinister music playing]
What is this?
[music continues to play]
[thunder roars]
[sinister music playing]
-[glass shattering]
-[Randall] Evelyn!
[Evelyn] Way too late.
Time's over.
[Randall]
Edgar, hold her!
Please, hear us!
[Evelyn]
Nobody's listening!
[indiscernible speech]
[Evelyn laughs]
[Randall]
Surrender her! Don't listen.
By the power of God,
surrender her.
[Evelyn]
You don't stand a chance!
[indiscernible speech]
Oh, shit. Fuck!
I don't have my keys.
-[loud growls]
-[glass shatters]
[Randall]
Oh, huh, wait!
[Evelyn grunts]
Just get your fucking keys
and get outta here.
[indistinct speech]
[Randall]
Oh, God, thrust into Hell
Satan and all evil spirits
who wander through the world
for the ruin of souls.
Amen.
[Evelyn]
Stupid priest.
[Randall]
Evelyn, stop.
Be careful!
[Evelyn]
Get outta here!
Evelyn, fight it.
I know you can.
In the name of God, the Father,
Jesus Christ the Son,
and by the power
of the Holy Spirit,
you will obey me,
you foul thing.
God cast you into a pit
of hellfire, into that pit
you shall return.
Oh, I can already
feel her suffering.
Evelyn is stronger
than you will ever be.
That's not
who I'm talking about.
Your daughter
is in eternal torture,
because of you.
You failed her, but I,
I can bring her peace.
[speaks foreign language]
-Don't listen to it.
-[Evelyn laughs]
Leave the flesh
of God's righteous creature
and return to the darkness
from whence you came!
Ah, your souls or hers!
-Little Sarah's blossoming
into a lovely woman.
-Shut your mouth, demon!
Oh, you should be honored
to have made
such a precious sacrifice
for me.
I have them both now,
and Evelyn has given up
her defiance
and replaced it with screams.
It's a sweet symphony!
Evie, fight it.
You're stronger than this thing.
You told me that you
found a way and you did.
But I need your help,
so fight it.
Fight it for her!
Fight it for all of us!
The blood of Christ
seals the cage.
By all that's holy in the power
of the Kingdom of Heaven,
I banish you!
Return to your prison.
[groans]
Your soul's it is.
[screams]
[flesh ripping]
[sinister music playing]
[screams and flesh ripping
continue]
[loud screeches]
[crying]
Make it stop.
[screaming]
[sinister music playing]
[thunder roaring]
[panting]
[keys jingle]
[Julia sobbing]
[sinister music playing]
[music continues to play]
[whimpers]
What have you done, Evelyn?
[sinister music playing]
[gasps]
[Randall]
You can't leave.
We need to get you
to a hospital.
Come on, let's get you
to my car.
I can't.
Just try
or you'll bleed to death.
Please, help me save her.
What is wrong with you people?
When this is over, bury it.
What?
When everything is done,
put it in the ground.
It's just like in the basement.
Like, what these?
Yeah.
And then-- and then--
and then,
there were these letters.
E-L-I-M.
Elim.
What does it mean?
We need to hurry.
[grunts]
No. No, please, let me go.
You can't go.
My dad needs me.
Don't let Evelyn die alone.
Come with me.
Listen, a Christian
ritual's satanic,
but if Elim seals the cage,
Satanism names our power.
I can kill this thing.
I don't wanna do it.
[Julia crying]
[Randall grunts]
No, I don't wanna--
I don't wanna do it.
[Julia sobs]
It should be a perfect fit.
Where do we-- wait.
Where are you--
Where are you going?
[Julia sobs]
[Julia]
Just let me leave.
Please.
[Julia crying]
[neck twists]
[Julia]
No!
[Evelyn laughs]
[crying]
[chains rattle]
[Evelyn]
Julia? Oh, Julia?
Don't be afraid, darling Julia.
Your mother wasn't.
She wasn't afraid to die.
She was heartbroken.
And I know her pain.
You don't know my mother.
[Evelyn]
I know her suffering.
And soon you'll have yours!
Go away!
[crying]
[sinister music playing]
Okay.
We're doing...
[crying]
[Evelyn laughing]
Where did it go?
Where does it fucking fit?
What am I supposed to do?
[crying]
[Evelyn] Oh, no, we won't be
needing that anymore.
Tell me, Julia,
would you trade your soul
for hers?
I'm not cutting
any deals with you!
You've abandoned her
like your mother.
[screams]
[Evelyn laughs]
[grunts]
The human body is much more fun
than a little statue.
And this one is very tired.
Let her go!
I intend to.
[laughs]
What do you want?
Right now, you!
[screams]
[chokes]
[sinister music playing]
Sarah doesn't blame you.
[groans]
It was never your fault.
[loud growls and screeches]
[sinister music playing]
[gasps]
[coughing]
[groans]
We did it. We did it.
I'm free.
[crying]
I think I need a hospital.
Wait, I don't, I don't feel...
-[hits]
-[yelps]
What's happening?
[Evelyn] I'm sorry.
It has to be this way.
What are you doing?
The only way is if it dies
inside a living vessel.
I have to do it now
while it's weak.
Or before I forget.
[Julia] Please.
[laughs]
You have been the answer
to all my prayers.
[screams]
No!
[groans]
[screams]
Please, don't kill me!
[entity]
Not again!
[screaming]
[Evelyn shushing]
[entity]
No!
Please, stop!
[screaming]
[Sarah]
Please, don't!
[entity]
Please, don't kill me!
Help me!
[shushes]
[Sarah]
Mommy!
Help! Please, help!
[Sarah]
Mommy, please help!
[entity]
Evelyn, what are you doing?
[Sarah]
Help, help!
[entity]
You cannot bury me again.
[entity groaning and screaming]
[humming]
[entity]
Evelyn!
[Sarah]
Don't!
[humming continues]
[sinister music playing]
[takes a deep breath]
♪ Take the name of Jesus
with you ♪
♪ Child of sorrow and of woe ♪
♪ It will joy
and comfort give you ♪
♪ Take it then
wherever you go ♪
-♪ Precious name ♪
-♪ Oh, how sweet ♪
♪ Hope of Earth
and joy of Heav'n... ♪
[Sarah screams]
[sinister music playing]
[intense music playing]
[music continues to play]